Connie Regan-Blake collection, 1974-2014
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 4: Moving Images, 1980-2007
  - Pennies, pets, and peanut butter: stories for children 1994, 1 videocassette (VHS; 30 min.): analog. (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV03)
    1 videocassette of the Folktellers performing children stories
  - Pennies, pets, and peanut butter: stories for children, 1 videocassette (VHS): analog. (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV04)
    1 videocassette of the Folktellers performing children stories.
  - Celebration of storytelling, 1 videocassette (VHS): analog (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV05)
    ABCCM Celebration of Storytelling. S and S Video Concepts, Asheville, North Carolina, 28803.
  - The Hogaphone and other stories, 1 videocassette (VHS; 30 min.): analog. (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV06)
    David Holt tells four stories: The first motorcade, The hambone fan, The hogaphone, Barney McCabe, and The water tower. 1991, High Windy Video, Fairview, North Carolina, 28730.
  - With a dog's eyes: capturing the life of Morris Frank, 1 videocassette (VHS; 56:26 min.): analog (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV07)
    An autographed copy of Bill Money's, With a dog's eyes: capturing the life of Morris Frank. Bill Mooney's monologue retells the story of Morris Frank who was the first person to use a Seeing Eye dog. New Jersey's public telecommunication network and New York Television of Lebanon, New Jersey.
  - Once upon a time..., 1 videocassette (VHS): analog (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV08)
    The Spellbinders program of community building through storytelling. Produced by Spellbinders Woody Creek, Colorado, 81656.
  - Mosquitoes and high water, 1 videocassette (VHS): analog (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV09)
    The story of Mosquito and high water.
  - Huchoosedah: traditions of the heart, 1 videocassette (VHS; 57 min.): analog. (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV10)
  - Folkways: The Storytellers, 1 videocassette (VHS): analog (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV11)
    A production of UNC TV, 1998. Research Triangle Park, North Carolina, 27709.
  - August Heritage Festival, 1 videocassette (VHS): analog. (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV12)
    Connie Regan-Blake telling the story, Oliver Hyde.
  - Worth Quoting and Kalliope, 1 videocassette (VHS): analog (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV13)
    Folktellers, 1993 Florida Community College at Jacksonville.
  - The 20th Anniversary National Storytelling Festival: Commemorative Documentary, 1 videocassette (VHS; 20 min.): analog. (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV14)
    Hometown Entertainment presents a full videotaped recording of the 20th Anniversary of the National Storytelling Festival. Published by August House, 1995.
  - Who made this mess?, 1 videocassette (VHS; 55 min.): analog (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV15)
    An autographed copy of, Who made this mess by Bill Harley. A and M Video, 1992, Hollywood, California, 90078.
  - An Interview with Odds Bodkin, Talesman, 1 videocassette (VHS): analog. (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV16)
  - Stories, 1 videocassette (Beta): analog (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV17)
  - Storytelling performance, 1 videocassette (VHS): analog (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV18)
    Storytelling by Connie and Barbara, July, 1995.
  - Barbara on CNN (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV19)
    Barbara and Billy Graham on CNN along with 20/20 and Stories on PBS.
  - Winter concert, 1 videocassette (VHS): analog (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV20)
    Winter Concert 86-87. Note displays that school and library is not of good quality.
  - Halloween concert at Camp Rockmont, 1 videocassette (VHS): analog (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV21)
    Folktellers perform Halloween Concert at Camp Rockmont, October 31, 1990.
  - Gamble Rogers (on S.C. Pub TV), 1 videocassette (VHS): analog (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV22)
  - Concert, 1 videocassette (VHS): analog (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV23)
  - Performance at Black Mountain Middle School, 1 videocassette (VHS): analog. (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV24)
    The Folktellers at Black Mountain Middle School grades 6-8, December 15, 1988, North Carolina. Duplicate recording exist. Inquire in AFC Reading Room.
  - Oprah appearance, 1 videocassette (VHS): analog (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV25)
  - Lisa and Aron's story - A journey of remembrance, 1 videocassette (VHS): analog (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV26)
  - Tape for B and C video, 1 videocassette (VHS): analog (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV27)
  - Ki Performance Group, 1 videocassette (VHS): analog (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV28)
    Demo of stories by Julie Portman and Paul Reisler. Ki Theatre/Zoidsongs, 1990.
  - United States of ASL Poetry and other tales, 1 videocassette (VHS 55 min): analog (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV29)
    Peter Cook tells five stories in American Sign Language. P.C. Productions, Chicago, Illinois, 1998.
  - A bell for shorty, 1 videocassette (VHS): analog (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV30)
    An original Story by Jim May.
  - Storytelling performance in Las Vegas, 1 videocassette (VHS): analog. (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV31)
    The Folktellers tell three stories in Las Vegas, 1993.
  - Balloon ride, 1 videocassette (VHS): analog (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV32)
    Folktellers at the 15th year of the Balloon Festival, October, 1990.
  - Augusta Baker: Celebrating America's Storyteller, 1 videocassette (VHS 17:05 min.): analog (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV33)
    Produced for the 10th Anniversary of the Augusta Baker's Dozen Storytelling Festival by the College of Library and Science University of South Carolina and Richland County Public Library, 1996.
  - Never Stop Learning (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV34)
    Channel 13, April 16, 1995.
  - Philadelphia Folk Festival, 1 videocassette (VHS): analog. (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV35)
    Original recording, August, 1984.
  - Visit with Ray Hicks/NAPPS Festival, 1 videocassette (VHS): analog. (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV36)
    Recording of visit with Ray Hicks (September, 1992) along with a recording of the NAPPS Festival (October 1992).
  - NAPPS Festival, 1 videocassette (VHS): analog. (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV37)
    Recordings of the NAPPS Festival, 1988, 1989 and 1990.
  - Workshop: Asheville Storytelling Festival, 1 videocassette (VHS): analog (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV38)
  - Folktellers, 1 videocassette (VHS): analog (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV39)
    Description on videocassette: Folktellers on PM Mag at Ba's Cabin and FAC about MST, July 09, 1986.
  - Ray Hicks, patchwork, and swimming in Cambodia, 1 videocassette (VHS): analog. (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV40)
  - Herman and Roma conversation with Connie and Nancy, 1 videocassette (VHS 1:30 min.): analog. (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV41)
  - Story of Herman and Roma Rosenblat, 1 videocassette (VHS 1:45 min.): analog. (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV42)
    Description on videocassette: a compilation of television appearances, school presentations, and family photographs, May 30, 2000.
  - Nordonia PM magazine, 1 videocassette (VHS): analog (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV43)
    Nordonia PM magazine in Ohio (several segments).
  - Blue Mountain Retreat, 1 videocassette (VHS): analog (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV44)
    Blue Mountain Retreat featuring 12 storytellers including Connie Regan-Blake, September 24, 1997.
  - Tales at Penn State, Erie, 1 videocassette (VHS): analog (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV45)
    Tales at Pennsylvania State University, October 24, 1995.
  - By word of mouth: storytelling in America, 1 videocassette (VHS): analog. (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV46)
    Compilation of performances and discussions held at the tenth National Storytelling Festival, Jonesborough, Tennessee.
  - Mountain sweet talk, Christmas, 1 videocassette (VHS): analog. (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV47)
    Recording of the play, Christmas, 1991.
  - Mountain sweet talk, 1 videocassette (VHS): analog. (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV48)
    Recording of the play, October 25, 1986. Taped by Isothermal.
  - Mountain sweet talk, 1 videocassette (VHS): analog. (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV49)
    Recording of the play, November 1, 1990.
  - Mount sweet talk, Christmas at Quality Inn Biltmore, 1 videocassette (VHS): analog. (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV50)
    Recording of the play, December, 1991.
  - Christmas at the Homeplace, 1 videocassette (VHS): analog. (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV51)
    Recording directed by John Basinger and filmed by Lynn Shaw, December, 1992.
  - Good Morning America Live Interview, 1 videocassette (VHS 5 min.): analog. (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV52)
    The Folktellers' live interview with Spencer Christian on Good Morning America, August 31, 1989. Duplicate recording exist. Inquire in AFC Reading Room.
  - Mountain sweet talk Act I, 1 videocassette (Beta): analog. (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV53)
    Recording of the play, October 25, 1986.
  - Mountain sweet talk, 1 videocassette (Beta): analog. (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV54)
    Recording of the play, October 26, 1986.
  - By word of mouth: storytelling in America, 1 videocassette (Beta): analog (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV55)
    Complete recording of the event.
  - Philadelphia Folk Festival: The Folktellers' live performance, 1 videocassette (Beta): analog (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV56)
    Recording of the performance at the Philadelphia Folk Festival, 1984.
  - Word of mouth - Folktellers' segment, 1 videocassette (U-matic): analog (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV57)
  - Augusta Heritage Festival, 1980, 1 videocassette (U-matic): analog (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV58)
    Recording of Connie Regan-Blake telling the story, "Oliver Hyde," at the Augusta Festival, summer, 1980.
  - Augusta Festival, 1 videocassette (U-matic): analog (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV59)
    Complete telling of Oliver Hyde by Connie Regan-Blake, August, 1980.
  - Teatown Video/Second Story/No News/Reel #47 and 48, 1 videocassette (Beta): analog (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV60)
  - Las Vegas Festival, 1 videocassette (U-matic): analog (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV61)
  - Workshop, 1976, 1 videocassette (U-matic): analog (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV62)
    Workshop, April, 1976.
  - Storytelling: tales for children and techniques for teachers, 1 digital disc (DVD 1:30min.): digital (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV63)
    Originally recorded in 1994. DVD produced in 2007.
  - NO UNITITLE INFO FOR THIS ITEM: PLEASE CORRECT, 1 videocassette (U-matic): analog (Item-id AFC 2015/003: MV64)
    No info.
- Series 5: Artifacts and Ephemera, 1979-2003
  - Pin, undated (1 of 12) (Box-folder 42/01)
    A pin from the Northlands Storytelling Network.
  - Pin, 1995 (2 of 12) (Box-folder 42/01)
    A pin from the Augusta Festival: Augusta '95 - Connie Regan-Blake, storyteller.
  - Pin, 2013 (3 of 12) (Box-folder 42/01)
    A pin from the Augusta celebration: Augusta Baker's Dozen: storytelling celebration 2013.
  - Pin, 1996 (4 of 12) (Box-folder 42/01)
    A pin from the Anniversary: 1996 (Augusta) Baker's Dozen 10th Anniversary.
  - Pin, undated (5 of 12) (Box-folder 42/02)
    A pin celebrating the Folktellers: The Folktellers: Connie Regan.
  - Pin, 1982 (6 of 12) (Box-folder 42/02)
    A pin from the 1982 Edmonton Folk Music Festival: Connie.
  - Pin, undated (7 of 12) (Box-folder 42/02)
    A pin for performer Connie 'Folktellers' Regan.
  - Pin, 1979 (8 of 12) (Box-folder 42/02)
    A pin for the Mariposa '79 Guest.
  - Pin, undated (9 of 12) (Box-folder 42/03)
    A pin with an image of Connie Regan-Blake.
  - Pin, 1979 (10 of 12) (Box-folder 42/03)
    A pin from the Mariposa '79 Performer 31: Connie Regan-Blake.
  - Pin, 2003 (11 of 12) (Box-folder 42/03)
    A pin remembering Ray Hicks, "Jack Tales Festival 2003: Remembering Ray Hicks, 8/29/22-4/20/03."
  - Pin, undated (12 of 12) (Box-folder 42/03)
    A pin from the Azalea Storytelling Festival, LaGrange, Georgia.
  - Hand-held Mirror, undated (1 of 2) (Box-folder 42/04)
    Mirror with the words, "Hold still! I can't see myself."
  - Hand-held Mirror, undated (2 of 2) (Box-folder 42/04)
  - Coin, undated (Box-folder 42/05)
    A coin with the words, "Stories for the young at heart - Krewe of Zeus."
  - Sticker, undated (Box-folder 42/05)
    A sticker, "American Library Association Distinguished Recordings: ALA Notable Record."
  - Pen, undated (Box-folder 42/06)
    A pen with the image of Connie Regan-Blake.
  - Hand-held fan, undated (Box-folder 42/07)
    A fan from the Doc McConnell Storyteller Old Medicine Show.
  - Brit rail pass, 1979, undated (Box-folder 42/08)
    A rail pass belonging to Connie Regan-Blake.
  - Bumper sticker, undated (1 of 4) (Box-folder 42/09)
    Bumper sticker, "Support your local storytellers,"-The National Association for the Preservation and Perpetuation of Storytelling.
  - Bumper sticker, undated (2 of 4) (Box-folder 42/09)
    Bumper sticker, "Have a good time in British Columbia."
  - Bumper sticker, undated (3 of 4) (Box-folder 42/09)
    Bumper sticker, "Support your local storytellers."
  - Bumper sticker, undated (4 of 4) (Box-folder 42/09)
    Bumper sticker, "The truth will set you free... but first it will piss you off!"
  - Cloth patch, undated (Box-folder 42/10)
    Brown and orange cloth patch possibly used to identify festival attendees.
  - Cloth badges, 1998, undated (Box-folder 42/11)
    Nine badges from the Glistening Waters Festival in New Zealand.
  - Cloth swatches, undated (Box-folder 42/12)
    Three pink swatches usually worn by The International Storytelling Festival attendees.
  - Styrofoam poster, undated (1 of 2) (Box-folder 42/13)
    Poster advertising The Folktellers' story, Tales to grow on.
  - Styrofoam poster, undated (2 of 2) (Box-folder 42/14)
    Poster advertising The Folktellers' story, Stories for the road.
  - Banjo strings (Box-folder 42/15)
  - Embroidered kit (Box-folder 43/1)
    Embroidery used in play as a prop. Cloth still in hoop; needle and thread still in gray cloth.
  - Oversize materials (Box 44)
    Includes childrens' drawings, ledgers, oversize color print and poster.
    Series 1, subseries A: Winter people, A poster advertising Winter People starring Kurt Russell
    Series 1, subseries B: Children's drawings, (1 of 5)
    Series 1, subseries B: Children's drawings, (2 of 5)
    Series 1, subseries B: Children's drawings, (3 of 5)
    Series 1, subseries B: Children's drawings, (4 of 5)
    Series 1, subseries B: Children's drawings, (5 of 5)
    Series 1, subseries F: Accounting ledger, 1984-1985 (1 of 3)
    Series 1, subseries F: Accounting ledger, 1995-1998 (2 of 3)
    Series 1, subseries F: Accounting ledger, 1995-2000 (3 of 3)
    Series 3, subseries G: The Folktellers, 1 color print 14x11 in.